<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Gotta Get It!!!]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Gotta Get It!!!]]></description>
        <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 01:57:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://noelssexyfit.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a939f953-9eac-4b84-9e40-48cc372dbb50.jpg" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/a-note-from-noel/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bba437ea-587c-4d23-b8e1-2a86e111c29e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 19:57:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-0lTpj-PsNGk/VyJLzu7-UjI/AAAAAAAAFgw/gBduNRq7r1UPLYH-rPuc_JzDa9W9dU4gA/w426-h930/16%2B-%2B1">]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/a2ec1d86-9e6d-43dc-917d-1619ba499260/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a2ec1d86-9e6d-43dc-917d-1619ba499260</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 01:23:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google Hangouts]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Google Hangouts</h1><p>Hangouts bring conversations to life with photos, emoji, and even group video calls for free. Connect with friends across computers, Android, and Apple devices.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/253bc4353ae00e2b81a567e8e37ba57090125216.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://hangouts.google.com/?hl=en&amp;authuser=2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b8870862-f689-43bd-975c-dc7038dcf34a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 02:43:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Merry Trotter is a 36yr mother of 5 who coaches from her experience through track and field (+10yrs), independent study (+10yrs), and a life time development of knowledge base on fitness, safety, posture, and much more. Sexy Fit is an original program built and developed by Merry. Sexy Fit sessions are kept small for better 1:1 encouragement on how to exercise for optimal results and improved safety.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/merry-trotter-is-a-36yr-mother-of-5-who-coaches-from-her-exp/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a5414dc-f712-4c24-97e0-a961c2ba3374</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:44:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>“I was born a fighter…Now it’s up to me to maintain & improve who I am, right now!! I can’t go back and change yesterday, or even a minute ago. I can only move forward. At times false beliefs of myself, of the world, who I am or who I can be… may try to get me down, but no longer will I give in!!! No longer will I be a victim, to anything, myself included. I am a survivor, a solider, a fighter. I have been redeemed through Jesus and his love for me. I will never give up and never give in. I am solution focused!!” Ms. Merry, Fitness Motivator.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/i-was-born-a-fighternow-its-up-to-me-to-maintain-and-improv/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">40d04c7e-1967-4db9-bc14-f9c399dd12e5</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:44:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>All Levels:These Sexy Fit sessions are challenging enough for the advanced participant, yet flexible enough for an experienced beginner. These Sessions include floor cardio, stepper cardio and small hand weights. These sessions have all the benefits of Beginners with less extreme challenges. Sessions can include Boot camp, running laps, light strength training, Pilates, core, back, and more Not recommended for those with no exercise experience</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/all-levelsthese-sexy-fit-sessions-are-challenging-enough-fo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5afe630d-5e53-4da3-ac26-dd2e8d450b62</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:44:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Moderate to Advanced: Recommended 6-8 wks after Beginner Sexy Fit sessions. Want more challenge well here it is. Ms.Merry turns up the cardio by including more stepper, floor cardio max, increasing weights, extreme core and working on every segment of the body. These sessions may have running laps, inch worms, burpees, Boot camp, and other daily surprises…Sessions are topped off with all the benefits of the beginner sessions, while stressing the importance of over coming challenges through positive thinking and meeting fitness goals. Welcome to work…Excuses are reasons for failure…Step up!! Always mixing it up to keep that body challenged!</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/moderate-to-advanced-recommended-6-8-wks-after-beginner-sex/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8f092b4b-c864-4749-8784-dec601c83b93</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Beginner: These Sexy Fit sessions are designed to get the body moving!! Is highly recommended for any new members or first time visitors. The sessions have special emphasis on the how to’s, to ensure exercises have maximized potential!!Lower impact, modified moves, on the floor cardio (1st 2wks) with all the benefits of specialized core, back, legs and glute workouts. Topped off with refreshing yet challenging Pilates!! These sessions do include an introduction to strength training (wk4) and more.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/beginner-these-sexy-fit-sessions-are-designed-to-get-the-bo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">26329891-faa6-4d06-a2f7-a5d4168fd599</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Speed Class: These Sexy Fit sessions are specially designed to just burn fat. High intensity floor cardio, stepper cardio, & core. Not recommended for beginners. No strength training (45mins).</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://noelssexyfit.com/speed-class-these-sexy-fit-sessions-are-specially-designed/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">01ac4211-db85-4483-970c-2e590abf1a28</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>